There is a small canal, it is a remnant of
存在一个小管，它是
this hyaloid vessel
玻璃体动脉的遗迹
and a fine canal currently remains in the eye
现在眼睛里还留有一个细小的管道
which leads us directly to a primary axis
它直接将我们引向一个重要的
important
重要
which is called Cloquet's canal.
轴线，我们称之为Cloquet管。
And you see it here, you see, it's a remnant in this
你在这里看到了，你看，它是这种
humor
体液中的一个遗迹
you have different humors
你有不同的体液
this is the humor
这是
aqueous and then the vitreous humor
房水，然后是玻璃体液
and the vitreous humor
而玻璃体液
you really have to imagine
你真的需要想象
that it's like a balloon
它就像一个
of gelatinous water
凝胶状水球
that is in the eye
在眼睛里
that floats
漂浮着
of water
水
with at its center
在其中心
a fine canal
有一个细小的管道
which comes directly onto the lens here
直接连接到这里的晶状体
You see, here, which is a direct axis with the
你看，这里，它与
optic nerve, or the hyaloid canal.
视神经或玻璃体管直接相连。
So the lens, it comes from your skin, surface ectoderm.
所以晶状体，它来自你的皮肤，表面外胚层。
Invagination, fifth week, lens vesicle is surrounded by vascularized mesenchyme.
内陷，第五周，晶状体囊被血管化的间充质包围。
Then, I have this connection.
然后，我有了这个连接。
Juxtacrine, the placode
旁分泌，基板
invaginates and will become
内陷并会变成
the lens. It's the same movement
晶状体。这与神经管的运动
as a neural tube. Poof, touc!
相同。砰，砰！
Inside, there remains a space,
里面留下一个空间
which we call the crystalline lens.
我们称之为晶状体。
There is a whole evolution of this crystalline lens
这个晶状体有一个完整的演变过程
which will form
它将形成
primitive lines, etc.
原始线等。
I will skip this part.
我将跳过它。
It's important to understand how it forms
重要的是要理解它是如何形成的
like a neural tube, and it becomes
就像一个神经管，它在这里
here, on its own.
独自形成。
It is truly the lens
它真的是一个透镜
of the eye.
的行为。
You see here the colobomic fissure; there is a line here
你在这里看到哥伦布裂，这里有一条线
below, you see, and that's what will later form, with the arteries, the canal of
在下面，你看到了，这就是以后与动脉一起形成
Cloquet.
Cloquet管。
It will close with the hyaloid artery and vein, which is central; this
它将与动脉和位于中心的玻璃体动脉闭合，这
important artery, this is a colobomic fissure in the eye
动脉很重要，这是眼睛里的哥伦布裂
that is not closed.
没有闭合。
What is this?
那是什么？
It is the primary lens vesicle
这是初级晶状体囊泡
which becomes a secondary lens vesicle
它变成了次级晶状体囊泡
with the lens placode; this is the crystalline lens,
与晶状体基板一起，这是晶状体，
juxtacrine, integration, you see.
旁分泌，整合，你看到了。
With the layer.
与层一起。
Here, which will form what we call, externally,
在这里，它将形成我们所说的，在外面，
it is the sclera, the first coat.
这是巩膜，第一层。
The second coat is here, all
第二层，在这里，所有
of this, in fact, is the choroid
这些，实际上，是脉络膜
which will form the attachment with the crystalline lens.
它将形成与晶状体的连接。
Anterior chamber, posterior chamber in the part.
前房，后房在部分。
anterior. So I can divide the eye into parts.
前方。所以我可以将眼睛分为
forward and backward, and in the anterior part, I divide it
前方和后方，在前方部分，我将其分为
into anterior chambers and posterior chambers. Then, we have
前房和后房。然后我们有
what is called the
我们所说的
conjunctiva, the cornea,
结膜，角膜，
which is in continuity, conjunctiva,
它是连续的，结膜，
cornea, and the cornea is in continuity.
角膜，角膜是连续的。
Continuity with the sclera.
与巩膜连续。
And what do we call the part here,
我们如何称呼这里的部分，那里，
the second, we called it the choroid.
第二个，我们称之为脉络膜。
We call it the uvea.
我们称之为葡萄膜。
And the uvea, it comes from the Latin uva, which means grape.
葡萄膜，它来自拉丁语uva，意思是葡萄。
This small membrane, like this, is a membrane very rich in vessels.
这层薄薄的皮肤，就像这样，是一层血管非常丰富的皮肤。
It divides into three.
它分为三部分。
parts, or into two or three major parts, which we call the choroid
部分，或两到三个主要部分，我们称之为脉络膜
here, and anteriorly
在这里，在前面
the cornea, and the cornea is transparent.
角膜，角膜是透明的。
But here posteriorly, there will be the iris, which
但在这里后面，将会有虹膜，它
is a continuity of the choroid, and
是脉络膜的延续，并且
we will have here connections, a ligament.
我们这里会有一些韧带。
which we call the suspensory ligament of the iris,
我们称之为虹膜悬韧带，
which maintains the iris,
它支撑着虹膜，
with small muscles called the ciliary muscles,
通过一些小肌肉，我们称之为睫状肌，
which will...
它们会...
We will see that in a bit more detail later.
我们稍后会更详细地讨论。
So the retina, in fact,
那么视网膜，实际上，
is the innermost layer of the eye.
是眼睛最内层。
Do you remember this first vesicle,
你还记得那个初级囊泡吗，
this small sphere that emerges,
那个突出的小球，
which we call the primary optic vesicle.
我们称之为原发性视泡。
which will make a movement like this, you see, like a
它会像这样运动，你看，就像一个
calyx, a vessel.
花萼，一个花瓶。
It is made of two layers, an inner layer and an outer layer.
它由两层组成，你看，一层内层，一层外层。
And this is where one understands what is called a retinal detachment.
这就是你们理解所谓的视网膜脱离的地方。